Guide to the Charles Davis Jameson Papers, Photographs and Photograph Albums, 1887-1919 and undated RL.11422
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photograph albums
  - Photograph album 17, 1890s
    - Chinese boats docked at large Western house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0275)
      岸边的船只和岸上的一处西式房屋
    - Canal gate from distance, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0276)
      运河水闸远望
    - Charles Davis Jameson(?) and a Westerner with bicycle, in a crowd, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0277)
      人群中的两个外国人，一个是詹美生(?)，另一个手扶一辆自行车
    - Chinese laborers moving earth with wheelbarrows, behind Westerner with bicycle, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0278)
      劳工们用独轮车运土，前面站着手扶自行车的外国人
    - Westerner with bicycle, along a path with Chinese, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0279)
      路上人群中手扶自行车的外国人
    - Chinese fishing net, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0280)
      河边撑起的渔网
    - Chinese laborers, some at work, some at rest, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0281)
      田野中有人劳作有人休憩
    - Chinese laborers moving earth in baskets, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0282)
      田野中劳动的人们用筐运土
    - Chinese laborers tamping the ground, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0283)
      夯土的人们
    - Chinese laborers beside the canal, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0284)
      运河边劳动的人们
    - Chinese laborers erecting telegraph poles, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0285)
      运河边栽电线杆的人们
    - Chinese laborers tamping the ground (close-up), 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0286)
      夯土的人们（近影）
    - Chinese laborers tamping the ground, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0287)
      Page 33. Version of RL11422-P-0283
    - Chinese laborers tamping the ground (close-up), 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0288)
      Page 33. Version of RL11422-P-0286
    - Chinese laborers preparing to move earth, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0289)
      田野中取土运土的人们
    - An expedition boat, with American flag, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0290)
      岸边的停靠的大船，船上挂着美国旗
    - Chinese man beside canoe, with cormorants, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0291)
      岸边小木船上的鸬鹚和船边的男子
    - Crowd of Chinese seated in front of houses at top of a slope, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0292)
      土坡上房屋前的人群
    - Crowd of Chinese beside rural town, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0293)
      村镇一处空地上的人群
    - Westerner along canal path, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0294)
      运河旁路上的外国人
    - Chinese laborers on a hillside, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0295)
      河边土坡上干活的人们
    - Chinese laborers, digging, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0296)
      挖土的人们
    - Chinese laborers, digging on a hill, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0297)
      山坡周围挖土的人们
    - Woman and a beggar beside a post, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0298)
      妇女和一乞丐坐在木桩旁
    - One Chinese child squatting, two other Chinese children standing, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0299)
      三个小童，一个蹲在前，另两个站在后
    - Chinese laborers at work, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0300)
      干活的人们
    - Chinese children, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0301)
      几个小童
    - Chinese men with baskets of food, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0302)
      一群人，箩筐中盛着粮食
    - Chinese beggar, leaning to left, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0303)
      乞丐歪坐着
    - Chinese beggar, leaning to right, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0304)
    - Two Western men, Chinese laborers tamping the ground in the back, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0305)
      两个外国人，后面劳工们在夯土
    - Rural Chinese houses, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0306)
      村中土屋
    - Chinese men, with rifles, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0307)
      一排手扶长枪的乡勇(?)
    - Charles Davis Jameson, beside a sedan chair, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0308)
      詹美生站在轿子旁
    - Harbor view, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0309)
      河湾
    - Harbor view, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0310)
      Page 38. Version of RL11422-P-0309
    - Chinese men in formation, with rifles and flag, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0311)
      手扶长枪打着旗站成一排的乡勇(?)
    - Group of Chinese near train cars, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0312)
      火车站，站在车厢附近的人们
    - Street scene with group of men near a house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0313)
      村中街道，人们聚集在一处房子外
    - Chinese men gathered around an outdoor stove, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0314)
      炉灶旁的几个人
    - Group of men with two sedan chairs, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0315)
      两顶轿子旁的几个人
    - Chinese man and boy with two Westerners, in a crowd, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0316)
      几个大人小孩和中间的两个外国人
    - Chinese man, kneeling, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0317)
      跪在田间的男人
    - Crowded street, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0318)
      街上的人群
    - Group of Chinese (at distance) beside house ruins, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0319)
      田野一侧一排残破的房屋和一群人
    - Horse corral, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0320)
      马场
    - Group of Chinese men and Westerners, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0321)
      几个中国人和外国人合影
    - Group of Chinese men and one Westerner beside a cart full of earth being pulled by oxen, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0322)
      装满东西的牛车旁站着几个中国人和一个外国人
    - Two Chinese men and a boy standing in a gate, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0323)
      院门口站着的两个大人和一个小孩
    - Human skeleton in a field, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0324)
      田野中的人骨架
    - Horse corral at a distance, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0325)
      马场远望
    - Crowd of Chinese, including children, entering a house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0326)
      院中的几个大人和许多孩童
    - Ruins of houses, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0327)
      残破的房屋
    - Human skull in field, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0328)
      田野中的骷髅
    - Man with baskets and three children, beside house ruins, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0329)
      一排残破的房屋旁挑着箩筐的大人和三个孩子
    - Chinese woman and two children, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0330)
      妇女和两个孩子
    - Crowd of men at entrance of village, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0331)
      村口处的人群
      Page 44.
    - Chinese men with donkeys, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0332)
      拉着毛驴犁地的几个人
    - Crowd at entrance of rural village, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0333)
    - Crowd in street outside a house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0334)
      房屋前的一大群人
    - Pit outside house, woman sitting on a coffin next to the wall, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0335)
      屋前的一个大坑，旁边靠墙有一具棺材，上面坐着一个妇女
    - Harbor, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0336)
    - House ruins along an almost deserted street in a village, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0337)
      村中街道两旁残破的房屋
    - Woman and child outside thatched house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0338)
      窝棚前的妇女怀抱婴儿
    - Chinese boats docked in shallow river, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0339)
      河边浅水处停泊的许多船只
    - Chinese boats docked in shallow water, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0340)
    - Western expedition boat docked with other Chinese boats, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0341)
      停泊的船只中的挂着外国旗子的船
    - Thatched houses beside river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0342)
      河边的一些窝棚
    - Young Chinese fisherman fishing with cormorants, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0343)
      两条渔船上的鸬鹚和年轻的渔夫
    - Young Chinese fisherman fishing with cormorants, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0344)
      Page 47. Version of RL11422-P-0343
    - Crops with hills behind, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0345)
      农田和远处的山丘
    - Crops with hills behind, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0346)
    - Chinese boats in river, with hills behind, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0347)
      河中渔船，远处山丘
    - Chinese boats in river, with hills behind, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0348)
    - Four Westerners in Chinese dress, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0349)
      穿着中式衣服的四个外国人
    - Three Western women in Chinese dress, with Charles Davis Jameson, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0350)
      穿着中式衣服的三个外国妇女和詹美生
    - Men with carts of supplies, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0351)
      独轮车运送物资，车旁的一些人
    - Three women and one man with Charles Davis Jameson, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0352)
      五个外国人：三个妇女，一个男士和詹美生
    - Chinese boats with sails unfurled, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0353)
      扬起船帆的几艘船
    - Chinese boats sailing, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0354)
    - Naked Chinese boy, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0355)
      赤裸的小男孩
    - Chinese man, in profile, reading at a desk, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0356)
      手拿书坐在桌边的先生
    - Chinese troops in uniform with rifles, in formation, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0357)
      身着军服的士兵，手持来福枪站成一排
    - Chinese boat run aground, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0358)
    - Chinese family outside thatched house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0359)
      茅屋前的一家人
      Page 51.
    - Charles Davis Jameson with Chinese man and surveying equipment, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0360)
      詹美生和他的中国助手站在勘测仪器前
    - Charles Davis Jameson, seated in Chinese house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0361)
      詹美生坐在屋中
    - Young Chinese boy seated at edge of Chinese boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0362)
      坐在船头的小男孩
    - Man eating food, beside baskets, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0363)
      男子蹲在草筐旁吃饭
      Page 52.
    - Three children and one adult manning a boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0364)
      大人带着三个孩子在划船
    - Chinese family outside thatched house, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0365)
      Page 52. Version of RL11422-P-0359
    - Chinese man on deck of boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0366)
      站在船上的男子
    - River's course, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0367)
      江面
      Page 53.
    - Chinese boy with basket, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0368)
      手拿竹篮的小男孩
    - Chinese boy aboard a boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0369)
      船上的小男孩
    - Passengers in a cart, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0370)
      车厢里的人们
    - Chinese boat with full sails, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0371)
      Page 54.
    - Child with basket, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0372)
      小孩坐在地上，旁边放着箩筐
    - Man with smoking pipe standing next to tree, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0373)
      拿着烟袋站在树旁的男子
    - Men on donkeys riding by man with smoking pipe standing next to tree, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0374)
      骑着毛驴的两个人，旁边是拿着烟袋站在树旁的男子
    - Baling hay, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0375)
      草垛旁的几只耕牛
      Page 55.
    - Harvesting a crop, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0376)
      收获庄稼
    - Harvesting a crop, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0377)
      Page 55. Version of RL11422-P-0376
    - Chinese boy riding an ox, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0378)
      田间骑牛的小孩
    - Team harvesting a crop, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0379)
      田间收割的人们
      Page 56.
    - Two boys with oxen, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0380)
      两只牛和两个小孩
    - Chinese beggar boy sitting in the street, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0381)
      坐着街边乞讨的小孩
    - Chinese beggar boy sitting in the street, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0382)
    - Chinese family on small boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0383)
      小船上的大人带着三个孩子
      Page 57.
    - Repairing a Chinese boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0384)
      修整木船
    - Repairing a Chinese boat, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0385)
      Page 57. Version of RL11422-P-0384
    - Man sitting on edge of Chinese boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0386)
      坐在船只一角的人
    - Chinese boats with dog along shore, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0387)
      停靠在岸边的船只和岸上的一只狗
      Page 58.
    - Two small Chinese boats, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0388)
      水面上的两只小船
    - Four Chinese men standing in a Chinese house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0389)
      四个男子在屋内的合影
    - Four Chinese laborers with harvesting tools, with two children standing at side, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0390)
      田里干活的四个人和一旁站着的两个小孩
    - Farmer guiding an ox, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0391)
      农夫赶牛犁地
      Page 59.
    - Farmer guiding an ox, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0392)
      Page 59. Version of RL11422-P-0391
    - Two men in military uniform astride a horse, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0393)
      穿着军服的两个人骑在一匹马上
    - Two oxen in water, with their handlers on the bank, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0394)
      水塘里的两只水牛，牵牛的两人蹲在岸边
    - Tree on hillside, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0395)
      小山包上的大树
      Page 60.
    - Close-up of tree trunk, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0396)
      树干特写
    - Small Chinese boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0397)
      大船旁的小船
    - Chinese man with his young child, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0398)
      大人牵着他的孩子
    - Chinese man, sitting, with smoking pipe, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0399)
      坐着抽烟袋的男子
      Page 61.
    - Chinese laborers carrying hay in baskets, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0400)
      挑着柴草的一些人
    - Planting rice, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0401)
      插秧
    - Chinese family aboard a small boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0402)
      小船上的一家人
    - Chinese troops around a table, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0403)
      坐在小桌旁的一些士兵
      Page 62.
    - Charles Davis Jameson seated with Chinese troops around a table, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0404)
      詹美生和一些中国士兵围坐在小桌旁
    - Chinese laborers carrying empty baskets, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0405)
      挑着空篮筐的一些劳工
    - Two Chinese boys carrying a basket, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0406)
      挑篮筐的两个孩子
    - Chinese laborers carrying baskets, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0407)
      挑篮筐的大人和孩子们
      Page 63.
    - Chinese boy with basket, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0408)
      坐在地上的小孩，面前有个箩筐
    - Chinese laborers planting rice, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0409)
      插秧的人们
    - Chinese laborers moving an irrigation machine on a bank, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0410)
      岸边操作水车的两个人
    - Four men eating rice at a table, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0411)
      围在桌边吃饭的四个人
      Page 64.
    - Chinese laborers planting rice, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0412)
    - Chinese man next to an irrigation machine, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0413)
      男子站在一个水车的旁边
    - Chinese laborers tilling the ground, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0414)
      犁地的人们
    - Pedestrian bridge over river, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0415)
      河上的人行木桥
      Page 65.
    - Bridge in Shanghai, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0416)
      上海的一座大桥
    - Factories in Shanghai, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0417)
      上海的工厂
    - Bridge and park in Shanghai, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0418)
      上海的大桥和旁边的公园
      Page 65. Version of RL11422-P-0416
    - Bridge and Hall & Holtz furniture factory in Shanghai, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0419)
      上海的大桥和旁边的福利公司家具工厂
      Page 66.
    - Edge of park in Shanghai?, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0420)
      上海？江边公园的一角
      Page 66. Version of RL11422-P-0418
    - Tree on grassy mound, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0421)
      田间的一棵大树
    - Chinese troops, with rifles, in formation facing camera, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0422)
      持枪列队站立的中国士兵
    - Chinese man on mat with hay, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0423)
      蹲在竹席前晒草的人
      Page 67.
    - Three women and one man, all Westerners, at a train station, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0424)
      火车站，一名外国男子和三名外国妇女
    - Charles Davis Jameson and three Westerners at a train station, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0425)
      詹美生和三位外国妇女在火车站
    - Chinese laborers removing earth from excavation, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0426)
      工地上抬土的劳工们
    - Chinese laborers preparing to move earth, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0427)
      Page 68.
    - Man in small Chinese boat, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0428)
      岸边划小船上的人
    - Man holding bowl, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0429)
      船边端着碗吃饭的人
    - Chinese laborers on earth pile, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0430)
      挖土抬土的劳工们
    - Front of Chinese boat, with men steering, 1890s; 5 x 4 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0431)
      河上驶船的人们
      Page 69.
    - Charles Davis Jameson sitting at a desk in a Chinese house, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0432)
      詹美生坐在桌边
    - Small Chinese boats along shoreline, 1890s; 4 x 5 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0433)
      河边停靠的小船和远处的村庄
    - Lifeboats on Western ship, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0434)
      外国轮船上的救生船
      Page 70.
    - Shuffleboard game on deck of Western ship, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0435)
      甲板上玩沙狐球
    - Western steamboat with sailboats in [Japanese?] harbor, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0436)
      日本？一处海港内的轮船和帆船
    - Docking in Japanese city, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0437)
      停靠在码头的船只，日本
    - Two Western men in rickshaws, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0438)
      坐着黄包车的两个西方男子，日本
      Page 71.
    - Japanese women walking in a street, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0439)
      日本街头行走着的妇女
    - Western man in rickshaw, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0440)
      坐黄包车的西方男子
    - Western man in rickshaw, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0441)
    - Japanese stone lanterns, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0442)
      日本石灯笼
      Page 72.
    - Japanese pagoda, 1890s; 3.375 x 5.625 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0443)
      日本塔
    - Japanese temple compound, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0444)
      日本一处寺院
    - Pagoda, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0445)
      塔
      Page 73.
    - Five military boats, with men standing at attention, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0446)
      五艘军船，船上有列队的士兵
    - Group of men at oars, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0447)
      大船上摇橹的人们
    - Boys and women carrying baskets on path to river, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0448)
      岸边挎着篮子走向河边的妇女和孩子
      Page 74.
    - Group of people in water, surrounding a boat, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0449)
      河里站在船周围的一群人
    - Small and large Chinese boats, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0450)
      岸边的大船和小船
    - Two Chinese boats under full sail, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0451)
      扬帆行驶的两只船
    - Charles Davis Jameson (at left) with Western and Chinese men gathered around tables, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0452)
      詹美生和一些外国人和中国人围坐在桌边
      Page 75.
    - Chinese boats in a row, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0453)
      河道上排成一队的船只
    - Chinese ship with two black sails, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0454)
      张着两个黑色船帆的大船
    - Chinese boat passing another boat filled with hay, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0455)
      两艘船，一只装满草
    - Chinese boats sailing in a row, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0456)
      扬帆列队行驶的船只
      Page 76.
    - Wall along river, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0457)
      岸边的砖石墙
    - Walls along the river, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0458)
    - Conduit into river channel, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0459)
      排水入河
    - Stone bridge over river, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0460)
      河上石桥
      Page 77.
    - Unidentified mountain, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0461)
      远处的山
    - Chinese boat and supplies on shore, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0462)
      停在岸边运送物资的大船
    - Westerner being carried in a sedan chair, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0463)
      坐轿的外国人
    - Machinery dry docked along waterfront, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0464)
      放在岸边的大器械
      Page 78.
    - Front of Chinese boat, 1890s; 3.375 x 5.625 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0465)
      大船的船头
    - Chinese boat with two women aboard, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0466)
      驶船的两个妇女
    - Three Chinese boats under sail, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0467)
      河面上行驶的三艘船
      Page 79.
    - Boats docked along river bank, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0468)
      停在岸边的船只
    - Chinese boats docked along shoreline, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0469)
    - Cropland in front of two mountains, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0470)
      山脚下的农田
    - Rock quarry with Chinese laborers, 1890s; 5.625 x 3.375 in. (Box 5, Album 17, Print RL11422-P-0471)
      岸边堆积的石材和许多劳工
      Page 80.